Guide to the Poetry: A Magazine of Verse Records 1895-1961
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1936-1953
  - Subseries 2: Manuscripts - Minor Contributors
    - Pr, Pratt, Charles Hyde Pratt, Lola Prevert, Jacques (includes Prevert poem translated by Lloyd C. Parks) Pribble, Emily Price, Edward Price, Richard Crandell Pritchard, Sheila E. Prussing, M. Jean (Mrs. David C. Burden) Pudney, John Puls, Helen S. Pyle, Barnes Thurman (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Q-Ra, Quinn, John Robert Quinn, Sister M. Bernetta Ragsdale, Eleanor Ragsdale, Willmott Rahv, Philip Raine, Alice (Mrs. Philip) (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Ra, Raiziss, Sonia Rajan, B. Rakow, Edwin Ramirez, Teodoro Estrada Ramsamuj, L. Sewak Chand Ramsey, Warren Randall, Julia (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Ra, Randall-Mills, Elizabeth W. Ratcliffe, Dorothy Una Rathner, Eugene Rawlings, John (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Ra, Rayaprol, Srinivas Raymond, Margaret Thomsen Raymund, Bernard (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Re, Reavey, George Reedy, William C. Rees, Arthur Dougherty Reeve, Paul Eaton Reeves, James Reichler, Melvin (?) Reid, Frederick Reid, John (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Re-Rh, Rella, Ettore Remenyi, Joseph Reninger, H.W. Replansky, Naomi Resor, Robert Reynolds, George M., SEE Lamar, Frances K. Rhys, Keidrych (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Ri, Rich, Adrienne C. Rich, Bertha James Rich, Daniel Catton (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Ri, Rich, H. Thompson Richards, Edward A. Richardson, Dorothy Lee Richart, Bette (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Ri, Richman, Robert Rickcords, Stanley Ridge, Lola (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Ri, Riggs, Lynn Riggs, A.S. Rilke, Rainer Maria Rips, Bill A. (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Ri-Ro, Risler, Walt P. Ritchie, David Ritchey Rittenhouse, Jessie Belle Rivas, Humberto Rivers, Lucia Riviere, Michael Roberts, Elizabeth Madox (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Ro, Roberts, Lynette Roberts, Martha Robins, Elizabeth Rodgers, W.R. Rodman, Selden Rogers, Alice B. Rogers, John William Rohde, Barbara (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Ro, Rolfe, Edwin Rolfe, John (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Ro, Romig, Edna Davis Ronald, T. (pseudonym) Ronan, Georgia Roof, Simons Rook, Alan Rosen, A.T. Rosenbaum, Nathan Rosenfeld, Isaac (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Rosenfeld, Paul (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Ro, Rosenheim, Ned Ross, David Ross, W.W.E. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Rosten, Norman (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Ro-Ry, Roty, Lee St. Ledger Roughton, Roger Roundy, Alice Rousselot, Jean Rubin, Joseph Jay Russele, Ada D. Russell, Peter Russell, Sydney King Ruthven, Madeleine Ryerson, Alice (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Sa, Sackler, Howard O. Sahl, Hans St. John, Emily Porter St. Ledger-Roty, Lee Sait, Elizabeth Sala, Anya P. Salinas, Jaime Salinas, Pedro (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Salomon, I.L. (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Sa, Salz, Mrs. Ansley K. [Helen?] Sampson, Ashley Sander, David (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Sandoe, James (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Sa, Sarett, Lew Savage, Robert M. Sawitzky, Susan Clay (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Sa-Sc, Sayers, Alfred H.P. Scannell, Vernon (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Sc, Scarbrough, George Scarfe, Francis Schappes, Morris U. Schaumann, Herbert Schmidt, Alex R. (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Sc, Schneider, Isidor Schoch, Hedwig Scholes, Kenneth Schubert, David (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Sc, Schubert, Judith E. Schuyler, James Schwartz, Irwin Scott, Aurelia G. Scott, Duncan Campbell Scott, Evelyn Scott, Frank R. (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Sc-Se, Scouffas, Roberta Scovelle, (Mrs.) Elton Scruggs, Anderson M. Scruggs, J.E. Seghers, Pierre (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Se-Sh, Seif, Morton Seiffert, Majorie Allen (Mrs. Otto) Selig, Richard Sergeant, Howard Shafer, J. Sinclair (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Sh, Shanafelt, Clara Shand, William Shane, Margaret Shank, Jon Beck Shapiro, Evalyn Shapiro, Harvey Shattuck, Katharine Shattuck, Roger Shaw, Carleton Ford (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Sh, Shaw, Francis Shaw, Louis Agassiz Shelburne, Mary Willis (Mrs. J. Croath) Shelley, Melvin Geer Shepard, Royal F. Sherman, George Witter (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Sh-Si, Sherry, Pearl Andelson Shore, Morris Short, John Shull, Charles A. Siegel, Eli Siegelbaum, Harold (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Si-Sl, Sillars, Robertson Simonds, Ruth I. Simons, Hi Simpson, Louis Simpson, Mabel Sinclair, Gladys Mellor Sinclair, Upton Sittig, Sigrid Slack, Charles W. (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Sm, Smith, Alice Gustava (Sister Maris Stella) Smith, Clara Williams Smith, Clark Ashton Smith, Gerald A. Smith, Israel Smith, James Steel (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Sm, Smith, Jerry Smith, Maude Sumner Smith, Robert W. Smith, William J; SEE Seghers, Pierre Smyth, Florida Watts Smythe, Daniel W. (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Sn-Sp, Snell, Sydney Snodgrass, W.D. Snyder, Emile Snyder, Jack L. Sokoloff, Benjamin A. Sopper, W.S. Sosland, Henry A. Sorenson, Virginia Soto, Fausto Spain, Richard Leon (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Sp, Spark, Muriel Spears, Woodridge Spector, Herman Spence, Lewis Spencer, Theodore Spingarn, Lawrence Perry (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Sp-St, Spire, Andre Sprague, Marietta Thompson Stafford, William E. (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - St, Stagg, Hunter Stanford, Derek Stanford, Don Stange, G. Robert Stanley-Wrench, Margaret Stark, Elva June (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Stark, Inez Cunningham (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - St, Starrett, Vincent Stauffer, Donald A. (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - St, Stearns, Florence Dickinson Stearns, Marshall W. Steedman, Marguerite C. Stefanile, Felix N. Stein, Arnold Stein, Gertrude Steiner, Francis George Steiner, Hubert (includes signed note from Thornton Wilder) Steiner, Jacqueline (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - St, Stella, Sister Maris SEE Smith, Alice Gustava Stephens, Bernice Stephens, William Stern, Richard G. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - St, Stevens, Thomas Wood Stevenson, Ellen Stewart, Desmond Stickel, Wolfgang Still, James Stillman, Frances Jennings Stoddard, Alfred Hazen (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - St, Stone, Ruth Stork, C. Wharton Storey, Violet Allen Storm, Marian Storrs, John H. Stoutenburg, Adrien Straus, Roger W. Stuart, Evelyn Marie Stuart, Francis Stuart, Jesse Stuurman, Edith (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Su, Sullivan, A.M. SEE ALSO OVERSIZE Sullivan, Mary Miller Sullivan, Richard Sullivan, Suzanne (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Su, Sundgoard, Arnold Sunega, Joseph Sutera, Marie J. Sutton, Homer Lee Sutton, Kathleen (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Svaglic, Martin J. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Sw, Swan, Emma Swan, Jonathan Orr (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Sw, Swartz, Roberta Teale Swenson, May (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Sw-Sy, Swift, Richard G. Swing, Bill Sylvester, William A. Symonds, Bernard K. Sypher, Wylie (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Ta, Tambimuttu, M.J. Tambimuttu, T. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Ta, Tanasoca, Donald Tanasso, Elda Tanner, Gwendolyn Tax, Ervin Taylor, Davidson (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Ta-Th, Taylor, Eleanor Ross Taylor, Mary Atwater Tello, Jaime ten Hoor, Frederick Terne, Doris Terry, Howard L. Tessimond, A.S.J. Thibault, Frank; SEE Weibault, F.G. Thirlwall, John C. Thomas Aquinas, Sister Thomas, Keith (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Th, Thomas, Rosemary Thompson, C. Endicott Thompson, Dorothy Brown Thompson, Dunstan Thompson, George Thompson, L. Thompson, Nora B. Thompson, T. Denis (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Th, Thomson, Rosamund Dargan Thorn, Michal Thorne, David Thorton, Amy R. Thorton, Monte (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Th-To, Thurber, James Tifft, Ellen Tindall, W.Y. Titus, Donald Todrin, Boris (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - To, Tomlinson, Charles Topa, John A. Torrence, Ridgely Towne, Charles Hanson Townes, Elizabeth H. (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Tr, Trapp, Jacob Travers, Elizabeth Treloar, Bennett Treuenfels, Rudolf L. Trewin, J.C. Trigg, Emma Gray (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Tr, Trilling, Lionel Trimpi, W. Wesley Trombly, Albert E. Troy, William (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Tr-Tu, Trueblood, Charles K. Tunstall, Virginia Lyne Turbyfill, Mark (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Tu, Turnbull, Belle Turnbull, Eleanor L. Turner, Nila Turner, W.J. Turnoy, Betty Tyler, Dorothy (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Ud-Va, Udell, Geraldine Ullman, Ardyth Kennelly Untermeyer, Louis Upward, Allen Urry, Peter Valéry, Paul SEE ALSO OVERSIZE del Valle, Rosamel Van Doren, Mark Van Ghent, Dorothy (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Va-Vi, Van Keuren, W.G. Van Slyke, B. Varney, John Veeder, Grace N. Velarde, Ramon Lopez Ver Duft, Lee Victorin, Annette Vidal, Amparo Rodriguez Vidaver, Doris Viereck, George Sylvester Viger, Mary Louise l (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Vi, la Villa Ronald Vinograd, Sherna Shalett Vivas, Eliseo (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Vo-Vr, Von Spee, Kurt Vowles, Richard B. Vroman, Leo (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Wa, Wagner, Geoffrey Wagoner, David R. Wahl, Jan B. Wahl, Jean Walker, Jiri (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Wa, Walker, Margaret Wallace, Michel Waller, John Wallis, Marie Pope Wallerstein, Ruth Walsh, Betty (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Wa, Walsh, Chad Ward, Addison Ward, May Williams (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Wa-We, Warner, R.E. Warren, Charles W. Warren, James E. Weaver, Edith Weaver, Richard M. Weaver, William Fense Webb, J. Roderick Webb, Tessa Sweazy (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - We, Weber, Brom Webster, Neil Weeks, Donald Weeks, Edward; SEE L Florence Weibault, F.G. Weinstein, Gloria Weinstock, Clarence Weisenthal, Morris (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Weiskopf, F.C. SEE ALSO Folsom, Franklin (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - We, Weiss, George; SEE Weibault F.G. Weiss, Neil Weisser, Jerome Welch, Marie de L. Wellek, Rene Wells Henry W. Wells, Marie Wells, Peter (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - We-Wh, Wendell, Jesse Read Wesenberg Alice Bidwell West, Jay West, Ray B. Wexler, Beverley Wexler, Irving Weyand, Norman Wharton, Will Whicher, George F. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Wh, White, Alison Genevieve White, Emily (Mrs. Harold) White Miles (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Wh-Wi, Whitsett, Gale Whittington, Robert Wieck, Fred D. Wiggam, Lionel Wilcox, Wendell Wilde, Irene (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Wi, Wilder, Amos N. Wilder, Charlotte Wilkins, Eithne Williams, Ann (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Wi, Williams, B.Y. Williams, Clinton Williams, David Park Williams, Elva Williams, John Williams, Louis A. Williams, Virginia C. (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Williamson, Edward (Box 82, Folder 9-10)
    - Wi, Williamson, George Wilson, David Hawxhurst Wilt, Napier Wing, Kleber Winocour, Jack Winston, Carleton (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Wi-Wo, Wintle, A.D. Wirtschafter, Reitza Dive Wirtz, Dorothy Wistrand, Robert Witherby, Diana Witt, Harold V. Wobber, Don (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Wo, Wolf, Leonard L. Wolff, David Wolfert, Helen (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Wo, Wood, Clement Wood, Erskin Scott Wood, Frank Wood, William H. (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Wo-Wr, Woods, John Wool, Sandra Worth, Kathryn (Mrs. W.C. Curry) Wright, Celeste Turner (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Wr, Wright, Frank Lloyd Wright, George T. Wright, Margaretta W. (Mrs. Raymond D.B.) (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - Wr-Wu, Wrynn, Mary J.J. Wrynn, Anthony Wurm, Ross (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Ya-Yo, YacShigar, X. Yakushigawa, Koichi Yarmolinsky, Avrahm. Yeats, ? (letter is from a London literary agency on behalf of Mrs. Yeats) Yellen Young, Anne W. (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Yo-Za, Young, Marguerite V. Young, Pearce Young, Stanley Zabriskie, George Zachary, R.Y. (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Ze-Zu, Zeisler, Erwin Paul Zilles, Luke E. Zinn, Mary Stockwell Zinnes, Harriet Zumbrunnen, Ruth (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - unidentified (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 3: Editorial Files
    - Sub-subseries 1: Correspondence, Notes, and Mockups
      - October 1936 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - November 1936 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - December 1936 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - January 1937 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - February 1937 (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - March 1937 (Box 82, Folder 27)
      - April 1937 (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - May 1937 (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - June 1937 (Box 82, Folder 30)
      - July 1937 (Box 82, Folder 31)
      - August 1937 (Box 82, Folder 32)
      - September 1937 (Box 82, Folder 33)
      - October 1937 (Box 82, Folder 34)
      - November 1937 (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
      - December 1937 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - January 1938 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - February 1938 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - March 1938 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - April 1938 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - May 1938 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - June 1938 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - July 1938 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - August 1938 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - September 1938 (Box 83, Folder 12-13)
      - October 1938 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - November 1938 (Box 83, Folder 15-19)
      - December 1938 (Box 83, Folder 20-23)
      - January 1939 (Box 83, Folder 24-26)
      - February 1939 (Box 83, Folder 27-29)
      - March 1939 (Box 83, Folder 30-32)
      - March 1939 (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
      - April 1939 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - May 1939 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - June 1939 (Box 84, Folder 5-6)
      - July 1939 (Box 84, Folder 7-10)
      - August 1939 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - September 1939 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - October 1939 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - October 1939 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - October 1939 (Box 84, Folder 15-17)
      - November 1939 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 84, Folder 18)
      - November 1939 (Box 84, Folder 19-20)
      - December 1939 (Box 84, Folder 21)
      - January 1940 (Box 84, Folder 22)
      - February 1940 (Box 84, Folder 23)
      - March 1940 (Box 84, Folder 24-25)
      - April 1940 (Box 84, Folder 26)
      - May 1940 (Box 84, Folder 27)
      - June 1940 (Box 84, Folder 28)
      - July 1940 (Box 84, Folder 29)
      - August 1940 (Box 84, Folder 30)
      - September 1940 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - October 1940 (Box 85, Folder 2-3)
      - November 1940 (Box 85, Folder 4-6)
      - December 1940 (Box 85, Folder 7-9)
      - January 1941 (Box 85, Folder 10-12)
      - February 1941 (Box 85, Folder 13)
      - March 1941 (Box 85, Folder 14)
      - April 1941 (Box 85, Folder 15-17)
      - May 1941 (Box 85, Folder 18)
      - June 1941 (Box 85, Folder 19)
      - July 1941 (Box 85, Folder 20)
      - August 1941 (Box 85, Folder 21)
      - September 1941 (Box 85, Folder 22-23)
      - October 1941 (Box 85, Folder 24-25)
      - November 1941 (Box 85, Folder 26)
      - December 1941 (Box 85, Folder 27)
      - January 1942 (Box 85, Folder 28-29)
      - February 1942 (Box 85, Folder 30)
      - March 1942 (Box 86, Folder 1-4)
      - April 1942 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - May 1942 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - June 1942 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - July 1942 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - August 1942 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - September 1942 (Box 86, Folder 10-13)
      - October 1942 (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - November 1942 (Box 86, Folder 15-16)
      - December 1942 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - January 1943 (Box 86, Folder 18)
      - February 1943 (Box 86, Folder 19-20)
      - March 1943 (Box 86, Folder 21-23)
      - April 1943 (Box 86, Folder 24-25)
      - May 1943 (Box 86, Folder 26)
      - June 1943 (Box 86, Folder 27)
      - July 1943 (Box 86, Folder 28)
      - August 1943 (Box 86, Folder 29)
      - September 1943 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 86, Folder 30-32)
      - October 1943 (Box 86, Folder 33)
      - November 1943 (Box 86, Folder 34)
      - December 1943 (Box 86, Folder 35)
      - January 1944 (Box 86, Folder 36)
      - February 1944 (Box 86, Folder 37)
      - March 1944 (Box 86, Folder 38-39)
      - April 1944 (Box 86, Folder 40)
      - May 1944 (Box 86, Folder 41)
      - June 1944 (Box 86, Folder 42)
      - July 1944 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - August 1944 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - September 1944 (Box 87, Folder 3-4)
      - October 1944 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - November 1944 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - December 1944 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - January 1945 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - February 1945 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - March 1945 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      - April 1945 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      - May 1945 (Box 87, Folder 12)
      - June 1945 (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - July 1945 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - August 1945 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - September 1945 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - October 1945 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - November 1945 (Box 87, Folder 18)
      - January 1946 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - February 1946 (Box 87, Folder 20)
      - March 1946 (Box 87, Folder 21-22)
      - April 1946 (Box 87, Folder 23)
      - May 1946 (Box 87, Folder 24)
      - June 1946 (Box 87, Folder 25)
      - July 1946 (Box 87, Folder 26)
      - August 1946 (Box 87, Folder 27)
      - September 1946 (Box 87, Folder 28-29)
      - October 1946 (Box 87, Folder 30)
      - November 1946 (Box 87, Folder 31)
      - December 1946 (Box 87, Folder 32)
      - January 1947 (Box 87, Folder 33)
      - February 1947 (Box 87, Folder 34)
      - March 1947 (Box 87, Folder 35)
      - March 1947 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - April 1947 (Box 88, Folder 2-3)
      - May 1947 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - June 1947 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - July 1947 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - August 1947 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - September 1947 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - October 1947 (Box 88, Folder 9-12)
      - November 1947 (Box 88, Folder 13-14)
      - December 1947 (Box 88, Folder 15-16)
      - January 1948 (Box 88, Folder 17)
      - February 1948 (Box 88, Folder 18)
      - March 1948 (Box 88, Folder 19-21)
      - April 1948 (Box 88, Folder 22-24)
      - May 1948 (Box 88, Folder 25)
      - June 1948 (Box 88, Folder 26)
      - July 1948 (Box 88, Folder 27)
      - August 1948 (Box 88, Folder 28)
      - September 1948 (Box 88, Folder 29-30)
      - October 1948 (Box 88, Folder 31-32)
      - November 1948 (Box 88, Folder 33-34)
      - December 1948 (Box 89, Folder 1-3)
      - January 1949 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - February 1949 (Box 89, Folder 5-7)
      - March 1949 (Box 89, Folder 8-10)
      - April 1949 (Box 89, Folder 11-12)
      - May 1949 (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - June 1949 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - July 1949 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - August 1949 (Box 89, Folder 16)
      - September 1949 (Box 89, Folder 17-18)
      - October 1949 (Box 89, Folder 19)
      - November 1949 (Box 89, Folder 20-21)
      - December 1949 (Box 89, Folder 22-23)
      - January 1950 (Box 89, Folder 24)
      - February 1950 (Box 89, Folder 25-27)
      - March 1950 (Box 89, Folder 28)
      - Case Against the Saturday Review (Box 89, Folder 29-31)
      - April 1950 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - May 1950 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - June 1950 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - July 1950 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - August 1950 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - September 1950 (Box 90, Folder 6-7)
      - October 1950 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - November 1950 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - December 1950 (Box 90, Folder 10-11)
      - January 1951 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - February 1951 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 90, Folder 13-15)
      - March 1951 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 90, Folder 16-18)
      - April 1951 (Box 90, Folder 19-23)
      - May 1951 (Box 90, Folder 24-25)
      - June 1951 (Box 90, Folder 26-29)
      - July 1951 (Box 90, Folder 30-31)
      - July 1951 (Box 91, Folder 1-4)
      - August 1951 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - September 1951 (Box 91, Folder 6-7)
      - October 1951 (Box 91, Folder 8-9)
      - November 1951 (Box 91, Folder 10-11)
      - December 1951 (Box 91, Folder 12-13)
      - January 1952 (Box 91, Folder 14-16)
      - February 1952 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 91, Folder 17-18)
      - March 1952 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 91, Folder 19-24)
      - April 1952 (Box 91, Folder 25-27)
      - May 1952 (Box 91, Folder 28)
      - June 1952 (Box 91, Folder 29-30)
      - July 1952 (Box 91, Folder 31)
      - July 1952 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
      - August 1952 (Box 92, Folder 3-5)
      - September 1952 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 92, Folder 6-10)
      - October 1952 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 92, Folder 11-14)
      - November 1952 (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - February 1953 (Box 92, Folder 16)
      - March 1953 (Box 92, Folder 17)
      - April 1953 (Box 92, Folder 18)
      - May 1953 (Box 92, Folder 19-20)
      - June 1953 (Box 92, Folder 21-23)
      - July 1953 (Box 92, Folder 24-26)
      - August 1953 (Box 92, Folder 27-30)
      - September 1953 SEE ALSO OVERSIZE (Box 93, Folder 1-3)
      - October 1953 (Box 93, Folder 4-5)
      - November 1953 (Box 93, Folder 6-7)
      - December 1953 (Box 93, Folder 8-12)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Galleys
      - October 1936 (Box 94 A, Folder 1)
      - November 1936 (Box 94 A, Folder 2)
      - December 1936 (Box 94 A, Folder 3)
      - January 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 4)
      - February 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 5)
      - March 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 6)
      - April 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 7)
      - May 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 8)
      - June 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 9)
      - July 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 10)
      - August 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 11)
      - September 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 12)
      - October 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 13)
      - November 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 14)
      - December 1937 (Box 94 A, Folder 15)
      - January 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 16)
      - February 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 17)
      - March 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 18)
      - April 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 19)
      - May 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 20)
      - June 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 21)
      - July 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 22)
      - August 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 23)
      - September 1938 (Box 94 A, Folder 24)
      - October 1938 (Box 94 B, Folder 1)
      - November 1938 (Box 94 B, Folder 2)
      - December 1938 (Box 94 B, Folder 3)
      - January 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 4)
      - February 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 5)
      - March 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 6)
      - April 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 7)
      - May 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 8)
      - June 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 9)
      - July 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 10)
      - August 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 11)
      - September 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 12)
      - October 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 13)
      - November 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 14)
      - December 1939 (Box 94 B, Folder 15)
      - January 1940 (Box 94 B, Folder 16)
      - February 1940 (Box 94 B, Folder 17)
      - March 1940 (Box 94 B, Folder 18)
      - April 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 1)
      - May 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 2)
      - June 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 3)
      - July 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 4)
      - August 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 5)
      - September 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 6)
      - October 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 7)
      - November 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 8)
      - December 1940 (Box 94 C, Folder 9)
      - January 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 10)
      - February 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 11)
      - March 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 12)
      - April 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 13)
      - May 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 14)
      - June 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 15)
      - July 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 16)
      - August 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 17)
      - September 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 18)
      - October 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 19)
      - November 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 20)
      - December 1941 (Box 94 C, Folder 21)
      - January 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 1)
      - February 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 2)
      - March 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 3)
      - April 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 4)
      - May 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 5)
      - June 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 6)
      - July 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 7)
      - August 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 8)
      - September 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 9)
      - October 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 10)
      - November 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 11)
      - December 1942 (Box 94 D, Folder 12)
      - January 1943, February 1943 SEE Subseries 1- February, 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 13)
      - March 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 14)
      - April 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 15)
      - May 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 16)
      - June 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 17)
      - July 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 18)
      - August 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 19)
      - September 1943 (Box 94 D, Folder 20)
      - October 1943 (Box 94 E, Folder 1)